<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description>A place to hear Alex talk</description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 09:43:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>nikola</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Kill Orcs &amp; Build A Better Marriage</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="round" src="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/OMDheader.jpg" alt="missing image"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you play video games with your significant other, then I have one question: have you two played Orcs Must Die: 2 yet? If you aren't, you're missing out on a truly great time with someone you love. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;It's Literally The Best&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I cannot overstate how much I love Orcs Must Die: 2. I won't bore you with a &lt;a href="http://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/orcs-must-die!-2"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt;, because I'm more focused on Orcs Must Die: 2 as a unique couples game, but it's a really great game besides. Here is a quick run down on why it's a good game to play no matter what:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Orcs Must Die: 2 hits every high note. The graphics are colorful and well used. If you enjoy games that use graphics to transport you, rather than impress you, you'll love the graphics in this game. The sound perfectly fits the world and helps immersion. Sound cues are also used, particularly tough enemies that target the player howl as they enter a level. There are a variety of items to use and almost limitless replayabiltiy as you mix and match more effective trap combinations. My only real complaints would be somewhat sluggish controls as well as horrible controller support. Overall though, I recommend anyone play Orcs Must Die: 2, even if you're forever alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a few things, specifically, that Orcs Must Die: 2 does well that recommends it for couples. First, of course, is the fact that it's truly cooperative, which is rare. Second,losing is fun, which is the difference between arguing over the defeat and happily starting another game. Lastly, and my favorite benefit: it offers a unique way to interact with someone you love, which is nearly priceless &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What's your point?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are lot of good games to play, many if not most are multi player. There are more ways than ever to play with your partner covering just about every genre imaginable. I think, and I will try to explain why, that Orcs Must Die: 2 goes beyond simply playing together and becomes and unique experience you can share with someone. The unique combination of tower defense and action gaming creates a situation where you actively get closer to your significant other as you game. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Co-op? What?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;True cooperative games are hard to come by, and they always have been. Don't let anyone tell you otherwise, those old NES "co-op" games were just two people on the same screen, there was very little actual cooperation. There is a difference between playing as a team and playing together. This goes for most games, really. Unless you've taken the time to practice acting as a team, your average multi player game simply pits people against each other, and some people (your team mates) can't be killed, so you vaguely work with them. More often though, in Team Fortress 2 for example, you work for and by your self. Orcs Must Die: 2 grades the team, not the person. Most other game there is a individual winner. In a "team" game of Battlefield there is a #1 at the end. The highest ranked person on the losing team still feels like a winner. He accomplished &lt;em&gt;his&lt;/em&gt; goal, so he won regardless of how his team fared. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A true cooperative experience means you depend on each other for a team victory. Whatever your individual accomplishments are it comes secondary to winning as a team. Look at team sports: even if you're breaking records you can't win without a team working as a unit. We've all played enough video games to know that good players can often carry weak teams on their shoulders. Before first person shooters matured into more complex games, you could win for your team singly handily if there was enough of a talent gap. If you want to act as a team, you worry about how other players are doing, not just your own performance.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you play Orcs Must Die:2 co-op you will find it almost impossible to win without your partner. Your items are halved when playing co-op, along with your in game currency used to buy traps. At the very start of the game you are dependent on your partner, you cannot win without them. So, first thing you have to do is start cooperating. What items are you buying? What traps do you want to use? Before my wife and I start a game there is a good five minutes just discussing what we think will work the best. This is followed by buying our items together to maximize our chance at a team victory. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The depth here is hard to enumerate. The traps, weapons, and trinkets all work together in unique ways, which is compounded when they are being used by another person. You absolutely have to state clearly how you are trying to accomplish victory. You'll start communicating with your partner, it might not be the most profound communication, but it's better than staring at two screens doing two different things. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Couples that lose together, win together.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It sucks losing, no two bones about it. We all hate losing and I don't know anyone but &lt;a href="http://dwarffortresswiki.org/index.php/Fun"&gt;Dwarf Fortress&lt;/a&gt; players who enjoy losing. It's fair to say that losing gets worse when you have someone to blame, and to blame you. I've seen grown men go red in the face, outraged at the poor play of a team mate. I could list games for hours that absolutely suck to lose and suck even harder because some idiot took the plane and crashed it into a mountain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not a great idea to spend time together, being frustrated at one another. That's not really hard to find, a long trip to Walmart should probably provide all the arguments your relationship needs. When you lose at Orcs Must Die: 2, it's more like a slap on the wrist than a smack down. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the two of you lose you'll laugh instead of growl. It's hard to blame anyone when you were both scrambling just to keep up with the enemies flooding you. There isn't time to fight over who blew it (the other person, of course) because you both want to get back into another fight. We don't argue because we are both excited about trying a new trap or trick. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When my wife continually falls into vats of lava (three in one game) I find my self chuckling. It's funny, theres not way around it. I know we should be working together, and we are, but it's just too damn funny hearing her mutter "fuck!" and then see her points come off the counter. I get my comeuppance when she has to save me from a group of monsters. (Monsters that I totally could have handled.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ten minutes later we've lost again, laughing, loading the level to take another crack at it. This is important. This cannot be under rated. There are a million reason to be frustrated with modern living. When you live with someone, now there are even more things to worry about failing at. It's a great relief to spend time together where it doesn't matter if you lose, it just makes the day more fun.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;You may not have seen this before&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people say it's wrong to be competitive, it's rude to have a drive to win. Often, we try to hide that side of our character, the part of you that wants to grind someone into the ground in triumph. Often it's frowned on to want to win. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bullocks. Not only is being competitive great, it's even better seeing the person you love getting riled up, ready to win. It's something you just don't see in a person all the time. If you play sports together, or often compete together, then this probably doesn't apply to you. Clearly, if you can work on a team together you know exactly how hot it is seeing your significant other just wailing on someone, and you don't need me telling you how great it is.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those of us of a more...cerebral temperament, don't have as many chances. It's not surprising, many of us haven't competed in &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; besides video games since we dropped out of fast pitch baseball. Our partners will tend be of similar temperament. I'm sure it happens, but I doubt it's common for the cross country runner to marry the avid gamer. So, it follows, that it would be hard to find a chance to really compete on the same team as your partner. If you haven't even seen the competitive side of your partner, you're missing out. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be amazed at how attractive your partner is when you're winning and losing together. It shouldn't be a surprise: for thousands of years couples have depended on one another just to survive, you often saw your partner giving everything they have to just to survive. Now, with the lack of struggle and the civilized nature of us spoiled westerners, it's more likely you'll see your partner struggling with a hard boss than struggling to overcome adversity. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Video games aren't adversity, but if you can't watch your wife kick ass at softball than a video game is the next best thing. My wife gets super angry when she loses and is highly competitive. It's even better when we're on the same team. She cheers me on, helps me, asks for help. When we go shopping, or live our daily lives its the steady route: we all just get through the day. Being competitive just isn't something you get to see. But it's fantastic when you do. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Play Games, Be Happy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn't advice, it's just one mans opinion. Don't try to solve a rough relationship with video games, any more than you would with booze or swinging. This isn't something that will solve anything for you, it's something that will add to what you already have. Do you love your boyfriend/girlfriend? Do you enjoy spending time with the person you love, husband or wife? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn't going to make a bad life good, but it will make a good life better. You'll love the time you spend with your spouse or partner even more. It's one more thing to share stories about, to look forward to, to enjoy together.  &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 18:47:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As long as he doesn't turn into Red Hulk</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="round" src="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/bbheader.jpg" alt="missing jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;That shit is called Bruce Banner&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.leafly.com/hybrid/bruce-banner"&gt;Bruce Banner&lt;/a&gt; is listed as a hybrid, but a strong sample will knock you on your ass like a good Indica. I would not recommend you get to know Mr. Banner if you have anything important to do the next few hours, including drive or think. In short, Bruce Banner is usually a high THC, high potency hybrid that sports thick red hairs and a black licorice smell. Leafly already has charts and a numbered system, so if you're looking for statistics it's already been published. If you want to know what it's like to actually smoke Bruce Banner, read on. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>weed</category><category>grinder</category><category>review</category><category>Bruce Banner</category><category>Medical</category><category>Dispensary</category><category>Chevelle</category><category>Cake</category><category>Sharpstone</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 20:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>