<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description>A place to hear Alex talk</description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 11:43:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>nikola</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Kill Orcs &amp; Build A Better Marriage</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="round" src="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/OMDheader.jpg" alt="missing image"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people think you have to have everything in common with your spouse for it to work. Others, many of the people I grew up with in fact, think that a husband and wife (or whatever arrangement works for you) should have almost no common hobbies. I've seen it both ways and for some odd reason it always seems as if they are &lt;em&gt;proud&lt;/em&gt; of their extreme position at either end; couples who spend a rare moment apart and those who rarely spend time together that isn't obligatory. Most of us will tend to fall into the average: you have your own identity but you enjoy sharing some of your favorite activies with the one you love. (love the one you're with!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you share video games with your spouse then I have one question: why aren't you playing Orcs Must Die: 2? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;It's Literally The Best&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I cannot overstate how much I love Orcs Must Die: 2. I won't bore you with a &lt;a href="http://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/orcs-must-die!-2"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; but it's important to note something: it's not just any shitty game that you can enjoy with your spouse. Orcs Must Die: 2 (OMD2) hits every high note. The graphics are colorful and well used. You don't see a lot of wasted effects or the ever lovely "lets make this game look like a J.J. Abrams movie" lens flare that's becoming popular. The music and sound are almost invisible, which means they are doing what they're supposed to. I enjoy the audio cues that alert me to special enemies entering the levels, but other than that I can safely ignore it. My only real complaint would be the sluggish controls. Overall it's a great game I recommend anyone play, spouse or not. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On to the meat!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's my point? Play this game and fall in love all over again, with your significant other. There are a few things it does especially well that lead me to the conclusion that right now Orcs is &lt;em&gt;THE&lt;/em&gt; best game to share with your lover(s). First, of course, is the fact that it's cooperative. Second, and this is a big one, your wife/husband/boyfriend/girlfriend might actually want to play this game with you! Lastly, and my favorite: it's genuine fun that you get to share with someone you love, across the room or across the continent. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Co-op? What?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;True cooperative games are hard to come by, and they always have been. Don't let anyone tell you otherwise, those old NES "co-op" games were just two people on the same screen, there was very little actual cooperation. Playing video games in the same room doesn't bring you closer to anyone. If you want to feel closer to someone try accomplishing something with them. So why don't most games fit the bill for co-op? There is a difference between fighting the same people and fighting together. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you play a normal multi player "co-op" game you are just playing at the same time in the same level. Classic Contra, for example, requires almost no actual cooperation. You both have to do your jobs, you can't let the other person down, but as long as they do perform well you can ignore them. I suck at classic Mario games, my wife has to carry me every time we play. I get bored to tears because we aren't playing together, we're just playing at the same time. She pushes us forward towards the end of the game but all we've really done is watch each other play a single player video games. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is co-op then, since you can Google it and get an easy list of "co-op" games? True co-op games means you can't carry your team mates: everybody has to do their job &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; work together in order to win. Most of your modern shooters allow a single person to dominate a game if they are good enough. In a true co-op situation your individual success should be dependent on the team as a whole. You can be the best Orcs Must Die player in the world, but if your partner isn't actively working to help, you are bound to fail. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;God, Not One of Those Games!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think it's safe to say that most of us are pretty picky about the games we play. Unless you are lucky enough to be young and to possess more time than you have any good use for, your spare time is precious. You want to play a game that YOU want to play, not pity playing some crap they bought. A person is allowed their preference and if you're significant other is a gamer they are sure to feel the same. If you're anything like me, your spouse has very clear ideas of what they will and won't play. She's an adult, she knows what she likes. But...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you come into the room with Orcs Must Die: 2 you've got some real versatility. It reminds me of Giants: Citizens of Kabuto. That also was a game that didn't really bother with a genre. It's not a shooter, it's a strategy game with some shooting in it. It's also not a boring strategy game like Dwarf Fortress. You like vanity items and customization? You've got that too. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally I don't think it's that much of a mystery of what girls want in games. Because they are people they want the same things we all want: quality, fun, value, nice graphics, etc. Girls only get different when it comes to details. Girls want them. The history of gaming for men is a history of games that are pretty barren. Most women need more context and control over personal behavior than the average man. If you don't believe me just look at the history of games. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As games have catered to more and more people, especially as they have catered more to both genders equally, they have added more and more of what most guys would call "fluff." Personally I've seen it to be true, the girl gamers I know like to change the way their character looks for more than just novelty. They also tend to look for more accomplishment than simply: kill all the bad guys because they are bad guys. My wife wants clear rewards for her work, Orcs Must Die: 2 gives it to her. She still doesn't care about the story for a multiplayer focused game, just like a guy, she just wants more than mindless killing and the endless hunt for more items and a more perfect character drive her on. Me, I want to see how high my life time kills can get. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Sharing is Caring&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's a real pleasure to get to see a different side of your partners personality. Playing a new game with your wife is nice, playing a game together where you have to use communication skills you rarely get to see with your wife or husband. It's not common for a married couple to consult on tactical issues. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 18:47:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As long as he doesn't turn into Red Hulk</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="round" src="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/bbheader.jpg" alt="missing jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;That shit is called Bruce Banner&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.leafly.com/hybrid/bruce-banner"&gt;Bruce Banner&lt;/a&gt; is listed as a hybrid, but a strong sample will knock you on your ass like a good Indica. I would not recommend you get to know Mr. Banner if you have anything important to do the next few hours, including drive or think. In short, Bruce Banner is usually a high THC, high potency hybrid that sports thick red hairs and a black licorice smell. Leafly already has charts and a numbered system, so if you're looking for statistics it's already been published. If you want to know what it's like to actually smoke Bruce Banner, read on. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>weed</category><category>grinder</category><category>review</category><category>Bruce Banner</category><category>Medical</category><category>Dispensary</category><category>Chevelle</category><category>Cake</category><category>Sharpstone</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 20:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>