<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description>It's a website! YEA!</description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 11:37:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola &lt;http://getnikola.com/&gt;</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A Tasty Sample</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/a-tasty-sample.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just put a little preview up on SoundCloud, check it out and be delighted!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/150938678&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_artwork=true"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/a-tasty-sample.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 11:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strange Dance</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/a-strange-dance.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Just a new song.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I put a new song up today &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/strange-dance"&gt;A Strange Dance&lt;/a&gt;. It's hard to describe, I don't really think about any sort of classification when I'm making a song, I just kind of go for it. This one definitely came out as a dance song though. Very lively, very happy. I used a lot of major chords, kept it very simple. I like songs like this, because there is a nod to the current trend in electronic music and dance music, but I think it's more musical than the stuff on the radio. There is a definite beginning, middle and end to the song. Overall I guess I made a dance song that I'd want to dance to, rather than a dance song that would be popular right now. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm terrible at promoting my self, and I'm trying to get better through this page. So today I'm actually going to remember to remind anyone reading: don't forget to click the &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; link at the top of the page as well as my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt; link. Follow me on both, it will make you feel toasty warm in your nether regions. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goodbye for now, don't forget to DANCE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/150916234&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_artwork=true"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/a-strange-dance.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 08:42:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You should've seen this coming</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/you-shouldve-seen-this-coming.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;First, the following:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a quick rant today. I uploaded a few new tracks to my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt;, got this website cleaned up and finally added all the buttons I want. I'm sure there will be more later, but for now this is more than enough. I think the next time I'm going to completely remake my web page is when I'm ready to have a "give me money for my music" link. Also, computers are just terrible. I encourage anyone who thinks that computers are "easy money" to spend their day forcing tools meant for &lt;a href="http://linuxfonts.narod.ru/why.linux.is.not.ready.for.the.desktop.current.html"&gt;Linux&lt;/a&gt; to work on &lt;a href="http://forums.opensuse.org/showthread.php/461353-10-Reasons-why-Windows-still-sucks"&gt;Windows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day I got &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/getnikola.com"&gt;Nikola&lt;/a&gt; working after trying to update it and the twenty some odd utilities and dependencies it requires to run the bastard. One of my best friends is a programmer (no link, I don't think he wants people to associate us) and swears by command line utilities. "Nothing is as powerful" he says, with a straight face. I have never had as much trouble making any program work as I have had trying to make a fucking command line utility to function. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At any rate, the page looks wonderful and I'll keep working on it. Either that or I'll finally break down and offer my friend sexual favors for a banging new website. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The "Facebook controversy"&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oVfHeWTKjag"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; concerning Facebook, content creators and advertising. Now, I'm not going to debate this video, I really just wanted to poke fun at anyone who didn't see this coming. &lt;em&gt;Of course you have to pay!&lt;/em&gt; What, did artists really think that they'd be able to use Facebook as a De facto web-page service and never be forced to pay? Facebook is a for profit company, and it was only a matter of time before they would spring on all the people using Facebook as their home base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case you didn't watch the video or haven't followed the uproar, the basic point is this: non promoted content is not reaching people as effectively as advertising. That's it. That's what people are upset about, up until now they thought they were getting a free promotion platform, no strings attached. Now they are upset and making an uproar on the Internet because they think that it's unfair for Facebook to promote paid advertising ahead of their user generated content. Personally, I think Facebook is acting exactly as one would expect a huge, expensive for-profit company to act. The people I'm upset with are the idiots complaining about it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Nothing is free. Nothing.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Really, the basic proposition is farcical if you write it down: creatives using Facebook as a promotional service shouldn't have to pay advertising fees to ensure that their content is seen by their followers. There are so many things wrong with that idea, I can't even get into them all, or even part of them. Really, I just want to make fun of all the pissed off people for thinking that they were getting something for free and that it would stay that way. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets break down exactly what they were getting:a free web page, and most of the benefits that come with it. That's what they were getting. It looked nice, it was stable, they had a web address they could send people to. They had as many or as few features as they wanted, all without any programming knowledge or outlay of cash. Basically they had a fancy Angelfire page that they didn't have to pay for. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, now you're paying for it. For years now people have used Facebook as a homepage and now it's not free, not if you're trying to use it as an advertising platform. Again, NOTHING IS FREE, why are people surprised by this? What incentive does Facebook have to be "loyal" to all these people? If anything, they are lucky Facebook doesn't just institute a pay to play policy for commercial uses. It would be perfectly fair for Facebook to impose a fee for people who are EXPRESSLY using their service to try and sell their content. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Get off your ass and run a real business&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What really chaps me about these idiots making an uproar, is that they are completely dependent on other people. No one even thinks of having their own website, yet any real band has one. &lt;a href="http://www.deftones.com/"&gt;The Deftones&lt;/a&gt; have a web page, &lt;a href="http://snoopdogg.com/"&gt;Snoop D, Oh, Double Gizzo&lt;/a&gt; has a web page. Check the link, it's his name. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So why would an artist think "Yea, I don't need a real web page to look professional, a Facebook page should do." Not everyone can program and not everyone can drop the money to have a professional web site created, but there are just thousands and thousands of ways to get your own web page without spending a ton. God help you, if you take the time you could even just make your own damn site. Hell, this is a static site I build using &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/www.getnikola.com"&gt;Nikola&lt;/a&gt;. It was a bitch to install but once I learned markdown it's easy as pie. Easier than pie even. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The point is, if you want to be taken seriously, you act like your business is serious. If all you've got is SoundCloud and a Facebook link, I think you're a joke and most other people do too. When independent artists push fliers in my hand and it has a Facebook address at the bottom I just throw it away. You're not a real band yet. Of course I'm not saying that &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; it takes to be a real band is a web page, but it's one of the steps. Get over it, you can't use Facebook as a free web page/advertising platform. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Oh Well&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll end my rant there, I don't really have a dog in this fight. I'm not performing yet, I've not got a following at all yet, but I have big plans and big ideas. I think about how I'm going to do it, what I need to do to get to the top. One of the first things I thought about to separate my self from the pack was my web presence. Thinking about that led me to the best question I can ask anyone who's pissed about Facebook:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If everyone else is already doing it, why did you want to do it too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/you-shouldve-seen-this-coming.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 15:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Missing The Point</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I uploaded my new track &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/clean-out-my-mind-1"&gt;Clean Out My Mind&lt;/a&gt;. It's a fun song, hopefully we'll see some action on the it. If anyone reads this and is interested in my other beats, I'm working as hard as I can on cleaning up my tracks and getting them ready. So be patient, very soon the world will be positively flooded with the sweet, soothing sounds of Al Hacha. As we speak I working on redesigning this site to reflect the change of focus and to maybe include some ways to buy my music, if you were so interested. Also, todays rant isn't so much pop culture as it is a personal gripe. Without further ado:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Onward!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm writing today about gear snobs. I frequent music blogs, forums and most often the popular rap production subreddit &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/www.reddit.com/r/makinghiphop"&gt;Making Hip Hop&lt;/a&gt;. I've noticed a trend amongst the users of my various haunts: the proliferation of gear heads. That would be their own locution, I prefer to call them gear dicks. These guys love hanging out and letting people know that without the right gear, well, you're just screwed. You'll never make music as good as other people, these people of course, unless you step up and buy thousands of dollars of gear to make music. What a bunch of bullshit. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;"It's just not the same"&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is their battle cry. "It's just not the same." They are referring to the difference between hardware music equipment and software music tools. To be clear, I'm not talking about recording. Only the &lt;em&gt;most&lt;/em&gt; hardcore gear dicks say you shouldn't record on a computer. It's just too damn easy, even your casual elitist won't argue that it's industry standard to record into the computer when you're ready to publish your music. Where the gear dick plants his flag is in the processing/creation stage. This means mixers handling synths, live instruments, turntables, effects boxes, compressors, etc... All the stuff you use to make or to alter music. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To clarify one more bit before I go off: I'm not talking about pros. A professional with a million dollar studio budget is going to have &lt;em&gt;everything.&lt;/em&gt; Why wouldn't Dr. Dre use anything and everything he can to make great music? No, I'm not talking about professionals with plaques on their walls. I'm talking about the very loud crowd on the Internet that spend their time crapping on new rappers and arguing with old producers about how you're just not going to get the same kind of sound without hardware. Again, what a bunch of bullshit. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;I didn't pick this fight&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These guys tend to be pretty similar category: they all have lots of hardware, have been doing it for a long time, and never got farther than the regional scene, if that, most don't really do much at all. Have I made it big? No, why would I waste my time with this blog if I had? I am, however, capable of noticing patterns of abuse and the patterns of the abusers. These guys all seem to be local/regional producers with thousands of dollars in hardware and not nearly as much to show for it as they want. When they spent that money, when they turned the spare bedroom into a studio, they did it with the intention of making it big. There is nothing wrong with that, I want the same thing, but looking at their posts it's pretty clear why they are so angry:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of them haven't made it and probably won't. I'm not sure I'll make a career out of music, probably not. That's why I, and  most others, focus on education over buying gear. These gear dicks are a small minority, they are just loud and annoying. They spent thousands of dollars over years and never bothered to get any better. Who needs to make new, interesting songs if you can side chain till your head spins? So now they have an entire Internet to bitch at to make them selves feel better. At best they get some local talent to let them make a few tracks, but it's much more common for them to languish in obscurity, firing at every fresh faced young rapper or producer who's trying to make it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The Equipment Doesn't Make The Music&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well shit, all that gear and you're not famous? What the hell? This is where the circle starts, you can look at years and years worth of Internet comments and blog posts to see the pattern. These guys are addicted, they keep thinking that the next piece of gear is what's going to make the difference and take them to the next step. They still play music, they probably spend quite a bit of time trying to improve, but to them the main source of improvement for their music comes from gear. Since gear is more important than &lt;em&gt;how to actually make music&lt;/em&gt; they focus on how to use their gear rather than on learning how to make music.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's a head spinning process reading these guys thoughts on the Internet. Even when people try to point out that it's more important to work on your self than on your gear they simply turn a deaf ear and continue. Voice sounds thin? Can't be you, it's gotta be the hardware, the process. Your mic isn't good enough, you need better cable, your mixer is washing out all your lows and that's why it sounds crappy. Same on the production side. The kick isn't hitting hard enough because you're not using the right gear. They might not tell you to get a full drum set, but they will damn well write reams about how it's just not the same as a &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; drum pad. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is how they answer literally, ever goddamn question. Even the ones they have no reason to comment on, they have to inject their thoughts on your lack of professional gear. They rarely run their own blogs, they rarely make the reddit thread. They know they would come off poorly starting a thread about how: "You guys suck for not having hardware mixers!" So instead they wait until someone asks something and pounce, declaring "You're never going to get it to sound right without (insert crazy expensive hardware component.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;My personal truth&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's why I call shenanigans: very few of us amateurs are ever going to make money doing this. It's the truth. I haven't made a cent yet and I probably won't, and that's a huge part of my complaint: they are honestly stating that you cannot make good music, music that people will listen to, until you have invested in expensive hardware. That's a key point, it's not just that you have a mixer, it's that you don't have the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; mixer. They tell everyone they can that you're wasting your time without gear, which, again, is so much bullshit.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, as you progress and your skills grow you will need more gear. I started out with nothing but a computer. Now I have a small mixer, a small midi keyboard, some electronic drums and a bass. I also have an old dynamic mic and a mic stand with a pop filter. Here's the thing though: My computer is still the most expensive part of this deal by far, and that's because it was a gaming rig first. My keyboard? The &lt;a href="http://www.alesis.com/q25"&gt;Alesis Q25&lt;/a&gt;, less than $60.00 on special. I have heard it said many times on the Internet that it's crap. Amongst the many good reviews on GuitarCenter, there were plenty of people bemoaning the poor quality of the keyboard. Hell, I actually own the thing, I could bitch all day, but I had absolutely no reason to spend more. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Same with my control surface:&lt;a href="http://www.korg.com/us/products/controllers/nanokontrol2/"&gt;The Korg nanoKontrol 2&lt;/a&gt; it was cheap as hell. I think my wife got it on special for $50.00 bucks. It's not nearly as nice as the Behringer BCF2000, at least according to the Internet and some reviews. But the superior controller also cost way the hell more and had a ton of features I would like, but have no real need of. I had some need of a control surface. I didn't need a full mixer, or sixteen channels. Hell, I'm a minimalist, I don't &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; 16 channels now. I won't use 16 channels right now, so why spend more?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The jerks who want to crap on you, gear dicks who insist that hip-hop can only be born of money, they want to make it too, but they haven't and they spent like they did, so they want to make sure no one else makes it. I hate discouragement, I hate elitist dicks who want to tell us what to do. This is 2014, I have a better chance of making it through skill, hard work and clever use of the Internet than anyone before has. I mean to make it, and to hell with the haters. They might have more gear than me, but when I listen to their music I'm doing things they aren't. Damn near everyone is better than the gear dicks. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Wrap it up Al&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, it's not a big deal over all. They are a minority. Most of the people on the threads are decent guys who don't try to discourage people. It's easy to ignore them and move on with life. Sometimes it just gets under my skin, so today I decided to bitch about it. I know they aren't going to change and I know it's apparently part of human nature to compete over material items, but it makes my blood boil when some half assed "producer" with more money than brains tries to tell me I can't be as good as him without his gear. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck them, they might have more gear, but I have a Rockband drum converted to midi, and a dick big enough to tell them I think they are ass holes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you leave, enjoy my new track:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/148542733&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_artwork=true"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 07:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moved On</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I moved, didn't have internet for four months, finally got it back up. Now I'm sorting through web stuff I haven't looked at in months. I am updating this page (work in progress, clearly) my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt; profile and my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; account. It's dreary work, I'd rather work on music than make new art assets, new content, update all my info etc, but this is part of the jam. I have no interest in trying to find a record company, so I suppose it's up to me to make all this crap happen. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what's coming? Well, eventually this page will get a complete re-do. I'm going to continue to use this as a blog platform, as I have so many wonderful ideas to share. Mostly though new music is coming down the pipe line. I didn't waste my time off, I've got lots of tracks I'm working on right now and it's just a matter of deciding what I want to polish up for &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt;. I'd write more but I spent four hours getting everything back up and running and I'm frankly sick of staring at Vim editors. Yes, I use Vim and maintain this website my self. Why, jealous?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>news</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 13:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kill Orcs &amp; Build A Better Marriage</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="round" src="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/OMDheader.jpg" alt="missing image"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you play video games with your significant other, then I have one question: have you two played Orcs Must Die: 2 yet? If you aren't, you're missing out on a truly great time with someone you love. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;It's Literally The Best&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I cannot overstate how much I love Orcs Must Die: 2. I won't bore you with a &lt;a href="http://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/orcs-must-die!-2"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt;, because I'm more focused on Orcs Must Die: 2 as a unique couples game, but it's a really great game besides. Here is a quick run down on why it's a good game to play no matter what:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Orcs Must Die: 2 hits every high note. The graphics are colorful and well used. If you enjoy games that use graphics to transport you, rather than impress you, you'll love the graphics in this game. The sound perfectly fits the world and helps immersion. Sound cues are also used, particularly tough enemies that target the player howl as they enter a level. There are a variety of items to use and almost limitless replayabiltiy as you mix and match more effective trap combinations. My only real complaints would be somewhat sluggish controls as well as horrible controller support. Overall though, I recommend anyone play Orcs Must Die: 2, even if you're forever alone.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 18:47:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>