<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description>A place to hear Alex talk</description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 21:12:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>nikola</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Kill Orcs &amp; Build A Better Marriage</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="round" src="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/OMDheader.jpg" alt="missing image"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people think you have to have everything in common with your spouse for it to work. Others, many of the people I grew up with in fact, think that a husband and wife (or whatever arrangement works for you) should have almost no common hobbies. I've seen it both ways and for some odd reason it always seems as if they are &lt;em&gt;proud&lt;/em&gt; of their extreme position at either end; couples who spend a rare moment apart and those who rarely spend time together that isn't obligatory. Most of us will tend to fall into the average: you have your own identity but you enjoy sharing some of your favorite activies with the one you love. (love the one you're with!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you share video games with your spouse then I have one question: why aren't you playing Orcs Must Die: 2? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;It's Literally The Best&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I cannot overstate how much I love Orcs Must Die: 2. I won't bore you with a &lt;a href="http://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/orcs-must-die!-2"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; but it's important to note something: it's not just any shitty game that you can enjoy with your spouse. Orcs Must Die: 2 (OMD2) hits every high note. The graphics are colorful and well used. You don't see a lot of wasted effects or the ever lovely "lets make this game look like a J.J. Abrams movie" lens flare that's becoming popular. The music and sound are almost invisible, which means they are doing what they're supposed to. I enjoy the audio cues that alert me to special enemies entering the levels, but other than that I can safely ignore it. My only real complaint would be the sluggish controls. Overall it's a great game I recommend anyone play, spouse or not. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On to the meat!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's my point? Play this game and fall in love all over again, with your significant other. There are a few things it does especially well that lead me to the conclusion that right now Orcs is &lt;em&gt;THE&lt;/em&gt; best game to share with your lover(s). First, of course, is the fact that it's cooperative. Second, and this is a big one, your wife/husband/boyfriend/girlfriend might actually want to play this game with you! Lastly, and my favorite: it's genuine fun that you get to share with someone you love, across the room or across the continent. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Co-op? What?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;True cooperative games are hard to come by, and they always have been. Don't let anyone tell you otherwise, those old NES "co-op" games were just two people on the same screen, there was very little actual cooperation. Playing video games in the same room doesn't bring you closer to anyone. If you want to feel closer to someone try accomplishing something with them. So why don't most games fit the bill for co-op? There is a difference between fighting the same people and fighting together. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you play a normal multi player "co-op" game you are just playing at the same time in the same level. Classic Contra, for example, requires almost no actual cooperation. You both have to do your jobs, you can't let the other person down, but as long as they do perform well you can ignore them. I suck at classic Mario games, my wife has to carry me every time we play. I get bored to tears because we aren't playing together, we're just playing at the same time. She pushes us forward towards the end of the game but all we've really done is watch each other play a single player video games. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is co-op then, since you can Google it and get an easy list of "co-op" games? True co-op games means you can't carry your team mates: everybody has to do their job &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; work together in order to win. Most of your modern shooters allow a single person to dominate a game if they are good enough. In a true co-op situation your individual success should be dependant on the team as a whole. You can be the best Orcs Must Die player in the world, but if your partner isn't actively working to help, you are bound to fail. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;God, Not One of Those Games!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think it's safe to say that most of us are pretty picky about the games we play. Unless you are lucky enough to be young and to possess more time than you have any good use for, your spare time is precious. You want to play a game that YOU want to play, not pity playing some crap they bought. A person is allowed their preference and if you're signifigant other is a gamer they are sure to feel the same. If you're anything like me, your spouse has very clear ideas of what they will and won't play. She's an adult, she knows what she likes. But...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me Orcs Must Die: 2 is like a buffet: there is something in the wide selection that she's bound to like. Neither of us is much for the modern shooters but other than that we play vastly different games. I will never force her to play &lt;a href="http://www.bay12games.com/dwarves/"&gt;Dwarf Fortress&lt;/a&gt; but I do want to play a game we both like, as opposed to another night playing different games in the same room while we watch season six of The Office. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, you'd like to &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/kill-orcs-build-a-better-marriage.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 18:47:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As long as he doesn't turn into Red Hulk</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="round" src="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/bbheader.jpg" alt="missing jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;That shit is called Bruce Banner&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.leafly.com/hybrid/bruce-banner"&gt;Bruce Banner&lt;/a&gt; is listed as a hybrid, but a strong sample will knock you on your ass like a good Indica. I would not recommend you get to know Mr. Banner if you have anything important to do the next few hours, including drive or think. In short, Bruce Banner is usually a high THC, high potency hybrid that sports thick red hairs and a black licorice smell. Leafly already has charts and a numbered system, so if you're looking for statistics it's already been published. If you want to know what it's like to actually smoke Bruce Banner, read on. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>weed</category><category>grinder</category><category>review</category><category>Bruce Banner</category><category>Medical</category><category>Dispensary</category><category>Chevelle</category><category>Cake</category><category>Sharpstone</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/as-long-as-he-doesnt-turn-into-red-hulk.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 20:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Test Post, Don't Upvote</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/test-post-dont-upvote.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;I can't stop talking is my "culture" blog. God I hate that phrase, but for lack of a better...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What can't I stop talking about? Nonsense that only other dorks would care about. I'm &lt;em&gt;deeply&lt;/em&gt; interested in Thor: The Dark World. I subscribe, and contribute to, the Dwarf Fortress subreddit. Speaking of reddit, I can't stop talking about trolling GTA V fans on /r/gaming. I often talk at length about craft beer or home brewing; I know very little about either but I do know how to drink awesome beer. I play video games, main stream and indie. I don't care about the console vs. PC fight but I love watching people fight about it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are lots of things I can't stop talking about. For the most part the things I talk about are pretty petty - mostly I pontificate on whatever entertainment media I happen to be occupied with at the moment. I admit that it's not a grand path, but I also admit that I'm not a grand person. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occasionally though, I will offer an insight of a more serious nature. I am worried about the state of the country and I will probably embarrass my self talking about it. I care a great deal about the culture I partake in, I'm a proud nerd I like talking about it. I worry too much about the state of the economy, the state of art in America, the consumer culture. There are &lt;em&gt;lots&lt;/em&gt; of things I care about. What do they all have in common? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know next to &lt;em&gt;nothing&lt;/em&gt; about any of it. I have no education and no training on how one would professionally critique anything at all. I can't solve any problems and I am certainly no great thinker. If I am a philosopher, then I am a poor one. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am, however, very passionate about all of it, all the stupid shit I pursue. My moods are mercurial and whatever I am interested in at the moment is what I love with my whole heart, for the moment. I've been a home brewer, an art student, a mechanic, a furniture mover and a laborer with a crew of illegals who taught me the Spanish word for prostitute. I role play, play video games, enjoy movies, TV, music and getting furious with strangers on reddit. In short, I'm not special at all and that's fine. Most people aren't special and as fun as it is to read articles by those who are inside the systems, those who get early game releases and private brewery tours, it's also worth hearing what a nobody thinks. We are all nobodies, for the most part. It's interesting to hear what a nobody thinks as long as that no body can turn a phrase. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And turn a phrase I can! Don't worry: I have plenty of stupid things to say and all the time in the world to say them. Take my hand as we explore the world of some idiot who can't stop talking, even when no body cares.    &lt;/p&gt;</description><category>introduction</category><category>new</category><category>first</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/test-post-dont-upvote.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 18:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>