<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking (Blog)</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/categories/blog.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 12:00:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola &lt;http://getnikola.com/&gt;</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Missing The Point</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I uploaded my new track &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/clean-out-my-mind-1"&gt;Clean Out My Mind&lt;/a&gt;. It's a fun song, hopefully we'll see some action on the it. If anyone reads this and is interested in my other beats, I'm working as hard as I can on cleaning up my tracks and getting them ready. So be patient, very soon the world will be positively flooded with the sweet, soothing sounds of Al Hacha. As we speak I working on redesigning this site to reflect the change of focus and to maybe include some ways to buy my music, if you were so interested. Also, todays rant isn't so much pop culture as it is a personal gripe. Without further ado:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Onward!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm writing today about gear snobs. I frequent music blogs, forums and most often the popular rap production subreddit &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/www.reddit.com/r/makinghiphop"&gt;Making Hip Hop&lt;/a&gt;. I've noticed a trend amongst the users of my various haunts: the proliferation of gear heads. That would be their own locution, I prefer to call them gear dicks. These guys love hanging out and letting people know that without the right gear, well, you're just screwed. You'll never make music as good as other people, these people of course, unless you step up and buy thousands of dollars of gear to make music. What a bunch of bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>rant</category><category>jerks</category><category>music</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 07:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moved On</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I moved, didn't have internet for four months, finally got it back up. Now I'm sorting through web stuff I haven't looked at in months. I am updating this page (work in progress, clearly) my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt; profile and my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; account. It's dreary work, I'd rather work on music than make new art assets, new content, update all my info etc, but this is part of the jam. I have no interest in trying to find a record company, so I suppose it's up to me to make all this crap happen. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what's coming? Well, eventually this page will get a complete re-do. I'm going to continue to use this as a blog platform, as I have so many wonderful ideas to share. Mostly though new music is coming down the pipe line. I didn't waste my time off, I've got lots of tracks I'm working on right now and it's just a matter of deciding what I want to polish up for &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt;. I'd write more but I spent four hours getting everything back up and running and I'm frankly sick of staring at Vim editors. Yes, I use Vim and maintain this website my self. Why, jealous?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>news</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 13:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>