<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking (jerks)</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/categories/jerks.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 12:56:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola &lt;http://getnikola.com/&gt;</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Missing The Point</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I uploaded my new track &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/clean-out-my-mind-1"&gt;Clean Out My Mind&lt;/a&gt;. It's a fun song, hopefully we'll see some action on the it. If anyone reads this and is interested in my other beats, I'm working as hard as I can on cleaning up my tracks and getting them ready. So be patient, very soon the world will be positively flooded with the sweet, soothing sounds of Al Hacha. As we speak I working on redesigning this site to reflect the change of focus and to maybe include some ways to buy my music, if you were so interested. Also, todays rant isn't so much pop culture as it is a personal gripe. Without further ado:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Onward!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm writing today about gear snobs. I frequent music blogs, forums and most often the popular rap production subreddit &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/www.reddit.com/r/makinghiphop"&gt;Making Hip Hop&lt;/a&gt;. I've noticed a trend amongst the users of my various haunts: the proliferation of gear heads. That would be their own locution, I prefer to call them gear dicks. These guys love hanging out and letting people know that without the right gear, well, you're just screwed. You'll never make music as good as other people, these people of course, unless you step up and buy thousands of dollars of gear to make music. What a bunch of bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>rant</category><category>jerks</category><category>music</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 07:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>