<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking (music)</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/categories/music.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 13:03:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola &lt;http://getnikola.com/&gt;</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Dance Floor For Your Feet</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/dance-floor-for-your-feet.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello, hello, hello! We're back again, this time with nothing but music! Behold, &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/dance-floor-produced-by-chef-f"&gt;Dance Floor&lt;/a&gt;, by me! With beats by &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/dance-floor-produced-by-chef-f"&gt;Chef F&lt;/a&gt; from his lovely new collection of hip-hop instrumentals &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/dance-floor-produced-by-chef-f"&gt;Aboard The Mothership&lt;/a&gt;. I encourage you to enjoy my song as well as Chef Fs album, both are more than worth your time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm currently working on a few comments about the brewing YouTube debacle, but I'm waiting for more information whilst I polish my prose. Until then, brave citizens, enjoy! Don't forget to sign up for my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt; for all the updates you'll see here, but in a much smaller form. Again, don't forget to follow me on &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt;, just to encourage you we'll exit on a song, my latest, Dance Floor:&lt;iframe width="100%" height="450" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/users/49201073&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_artwork=true&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>music</category><category>dance</category><category>Update</category><category>collaboration</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/dance-floor-for-your-feet.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 12:47:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Knock'n Boots</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/knockn-boots.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to all my fan(s?). Honestly, I'm almost certain no one is reading this, but it's fun to pretend!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of course, the new music: &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/lets-just-do-it"&gt;Lets Just Do It&lt;/a&gt; just "dropped" so to speak. It's far from studio quality, I know, but this is the first song I've been brave enough to publish with the vocals I recorded. It's not uncommon for me to rap over the beats I make, but I haven't ever done one that I felt could stand up to real scrutiny. By all means, this one could do with some scrutiny, but it could be a lot worse. It is about sexual congress, or "fucking" as the kids call it. It's not a curse laden &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u6VTj7LhCtE&amp;amp;feature=kp"&gt;2 Live Crew&lt;/a&gt; song, nor am I &lt;a href="http://youtu.be/Zyhu2ysqKGk"&gt;singing about juice running down my leg&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's odd, but sex is one of the easiest and hardest things to rhyme about. It's easy because, well, it's easy. Men think about it a lot, combine that with the ease of rhyming "ass", "fuck" and "titts" and you've got a pretty straightforward path. Any guy off the road could probably do a clumsy job of rapping about how much he likes Titts &amp;amp; Ass if you gave him a minute to think about it. The real challenge is talking about sex in a way that hasn't been done a million times already, but still comes off as clever. I mean, you could spend the entire song rapping about how big your dick is, which seems to be the most common go-to in rap. You could go the &lt;a href="http://www.cracked.com/blog/3-genius-artists-who-created-their-best-works-by-accident_p2/"&gt;Robert Plant&lt;/a&gt; route and try to make it "subtle". Either extreme and you're probably doing the exact same thing other people have already done. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried to split the difference. It's direct, there is some adult language, but I'm not falling over my self to make very explicit, gross lyrics. Everyone who's had sex knows the basics, I don't think you need me spelling out every step of the journey. Personally, I always got grossed when Easy-E put such detail and palaver into his sexual lyrics. On the other side, I'm not giving you heavy handed metaphor. This isn't the sixties, I'm pretty sure we're allowed to mention the fact that women can have orgasms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over all, I'm pretty happy with it. I hope anyone who gives it a listen enjoys it, and if so please don't forget to click the RSS button on top if you use Feedly, and give my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt; a jingle-jangle. If you want to speak to me directly &lt;a href="mailto:icsttemp@gmail.com"&gt;give my email a go&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/154358434&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_artwork=true&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>music</category><category>Update</category><category>new release</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/knockn-boots.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 11:20:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>More Serving, More Purpose</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/more-serving-more-purpose.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back with more noise for the holes in your head! Relax and enjoy &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/servile-purpose"&gt;Servile Purpose&lt;/a&gt;. I think it's about finished, so I'd like to talk about it a little bit, but first I need to do a little shilling!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone is reading this, and &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; should be reading this, remember to follow me on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt; if you enjoy updates and thoughts at random. Please, make sure to dish out the "likes" like it's candy, every bit of encouragement helps makes this work (and helps me sell it to the ball and chain.) People say all this social networking is vital, and I suppose it is, but I think it's more vital for an established artist than for a "in the making" sort of performer such as my self. Oh well, even if I'm shouting into the wilderness, at least I'm shouting. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/more-serving-more-purpose.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Update</category><category>music</category><category>Soundcloud</category><category>MTG</category><category>Card Games</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/more-serving-more-purpose.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 13:19:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Tasty Sample</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/a-tasty-sample.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just put a little preview up on SoundCloud, check it out and be delighted!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/150938678&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_artwork=true"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>music</category><category>Soundcloud</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/a-tasty-sample.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 11:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strange Dance</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/a-strange-dance.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Just a new song.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I put a new song up today &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/strange-dance"&gt;A Strange Dance&lt;/a&gt;. It's hard to describe, I don't really think about any sort of classification when I'm making a song, I just kind of go for it. This one definitely came out as a dance song though. Very lively, very happy. I used a lot of major chords, kept it very simple. I like songs like this, because there is a nod to the current trend in electronic music and dance music, but I think it's more musical than the stuff on the radio. There is a definite beginning, middle and end to the song. Overall I guess I made a dance song that I'd want to dance to, rather than a dance song that would be popular right now. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm terrible at promoting my self, and I'm trying to get better through this page. So today I'm actually going to remember to remind anyone reading: don't forget to click the &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; link at the top of the page as well as my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt; link. Follow me on both, it will make you feel toasty warm in your nether regions. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goodbye for now, don't forget to DANCE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/150916234&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_artwork=true"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>music</category><category>dance</category><category>instrumental</category><category>Update</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/a-strange-dance.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 08:42:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You should've seen this coming</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/you-shouldve-seen-this-coming.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;First, the following:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a quick rant today. I uploaded a few new tracks to my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt;, got this website cleaned up and finally added all the buttons I want. I'm sure there will be more later, but for now this is more than enough. I think the next time I'm going to completely remake my web page is when I'm ready to have a "give me money for my music" link. Also, computers are just terrible. I encourage anyone who thinks that computers are "easy money" to spend their day forcing tools meant for &lt;a href="http://linuxfonts.narod.ru/why.linux.is.not.ready.for.the.desktop.current.html"&gt;Linux&lt;/a&gt; to work on &lt;a href="http://forums.opensuse.org/showthread.php/461353-10-Reasons-why-Windows-still-sucks"&gt;Windows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day I got &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/getnikola.com"&gt;Nikola&lt;/a&gt; working after trying to update it and the twenty some odd utilities and dependencies it requires to run the bastard. One of my best friends is a programmer (no link, I don't think he wants people to associate us) and swears by command line utilities. "Nothing is as powerful" he says, with a straight face. I have never had as much trouble making any program work as I have had trying to make a fucking command line utility to function. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At any rate, the page looks wonderful and I'll keep working on it. Either that or I'll finally break down and offer my friend sexual favors for a banging new website. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The "Facebook controversy"&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oVfHeWTKjag"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; concerning Facebook, content creators and advertising. Now, I'm not going to debate this video, I really just wanted to poke fun at anyone who didn't see this coming. &lt;em&gt;Of course you have to pay!&lt;/em&gt; What, did artists really think that they'd be able to use Facebook as a De facto web-page service and never be forced to pay? Facebook is a for profit company, and it was only a matter of time before they would spring on all the people using Facebook as their home base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case you didn't watch the video or haven't followed the uproar, the basic point is this: non promoted content is not reaching people as effectively as advertising. That's it. That's what people are upset about, up until now they thought they were getting a free promotion platform, no strings attached. Now they are upset and making an uproar on the Internet because they think that it's unfair for Facebook to promote paid advertising ahead of their user generated content. Personally, I think Facebook is acting exactly as one would expect a huge, expensive for-profit company to act. The people I'm upset with are the idiots complaining about it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/you-shouldve-seen-this-coming.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Update</category><category>news</category><category>music</category><category>Facebook</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/you-shouldve-seen-this-coming.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 15:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Missing The Point</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I uploaded my new track &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/clean-out-my-mind-1"&gt;Clean Out My Mind&lt;/a&gt;. It's a fun song, hopefully we'll see some action on the it. If anyone reads this and is interested in my other beats, I'm working as hard as I can on cleaning up my tracks and getting them ready. So be patient, very soon the world will be positively flooded with the sweet, soothing sounds of Al Hacha. As we speak I working on redesigning this site to reflect the change of focus and to maybe include some ways to buy my music, if you were so interested. Also, todays rant isn't so much pop culture as it is a personal gripe. Without further ado:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Onward!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm writing today about gear snobs. I frequent music blogs, forums and most often the popular rap production subreddit &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/www.reddit.com/r/makinghiphop"&gt;Making Hip Hop&lt;/a&gt;. I've noticed a trend amongst the users of my various haunts: the proliferation of gear heads. That would be their own locution, I prefer to call them gear dicks. These guys love hanging out and letting people know that without the right gear, well, you're just screwed. You'll never make music as good as other people, these people of course, unless you step up and buy thousands of dollars of gear to make music. What a bunch of bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>rant</category><category>jerks</category><category>music</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 07:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>