<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking (news)</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description>A place to hear Alex talk</description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/categories/news.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 13:46:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>nikola</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Moved On</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;So I moved, didn't have internet for four months, finally got it back up. Now I'm sorting through web stuff I haven't looked at in months. I am updating this page (work in progress, clearly) my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt; profile and my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; account. It's dreary work, I'd rather work on music than make new art assets, new content, update all my info etc, but this is part of the jam. I have no interest in trying to find a record company, so I suppose it's up to me to make all this crap happen. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what's coming? Well, eventually this page will get a complete re-do. I'm going to continue to use this as a blog platform, as I have so many wonderful ideas to share. Mostly though new music is coming down the pipe line. I didn't waste my time off, I've got lots of tracks I'm working on right now and it's just a matter of deciding what I want to polish up for &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt;. I'd write more but I spent four hours getting everything back up and running and I'm frankly sick of staring at Vim editors. Yes, I use Vim and maintain this website my self. Why, jealous?&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>news</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 13:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>