<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking (news)</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/categories/news.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 08:10:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola &lt;http://getnikola.com/&gt;</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>You should've seen this coming</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/you-shouldve-seen-this-coming.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;First, the following:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a quick rant today. I uploaded a few new tracks to my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt;, got this website cleaned up and finally added all the buttons I want. I'm sure there will be more later, but for now this is more than enough. I think the next time I'm going to completely remake my web page is when I'm ready to have a "give me money for my music" link. Also, computers are just terrible. I encourage anyone who thinks that computers are "easy money" to spend their day forcing tools meant for &lt;a href="http://linuxfonts.narod.ru/why.linux.is.not.ready.for.the.desktop.current.html"&gt;Linux&lt;/a&gt; to work on &lt;a href="http://forums.opensuse.org/showthread.php/461353-10-Reasons-why-Windows-still-sucks"&gt;Windows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day I got &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/getnikola.com"&gt;Nikola&lt;/a&gt; working after trying to update it and the twenty some odd utilities and dependencies it requires to run the bastard. One of my best friends is a programmer (no link, I don't think he wants people to associate us) and swears by command line utilities. "Nothing is as powerful" he says, with a straight face. I have never had as much trouble making any program work as I have had trying to make a fucking command line utility to function. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At any rate, the page looks wonderful and I'll keep working on it. Either that or I'll finally break down and offer my friend sexual favors for a banging new website. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The "Facebook controversy"&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oVfHeWTKjag"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; concerning Facebook, content creators and advertising. Now, I'm not going to debate this video, I really just wanted to poke fun at anyone who didn't see this coming. &lt;em&gt;Of course you have to pay!&lt;/em&gt; What, did artists really think that they'd be able to use Facebook as a De facto web-page service and never be forced to pay? Facebook is a for profit company, and it was only a matter of time before they would spring on all the people using Facebook as their home base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case you didn't watch the video or haven't followed the uproar, the basic point is this: non promoted content is not reaching people as effectively as advertising. That's it. That's what people are upset about, up until now they thought they were getting a free promotion platform, no strings attached. Now they are upset and making an uproar on the Internet because they think that it's unfair for Facebook to promote paid advertising ahead of their user generated content. Personally, I think Facebook is acting exactly as one would expect a huge, expensive for-profit company to act. The people I'm upset with are the idiots complaining about it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/you-shouldve-seen-this-coming.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Update</category><category>news</category><category>music</category><category>Facebook</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/you-shouldve-seen-this-coming.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 15:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moved On</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I moved, didn't have internet for four months, finally got it back up. Now I'm sorting through web stuff I haven't looked at in months. I am updating this page (work in progress, clearly) my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt; profile and my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; account. It's dreary work, I'd rather work on music than make new art assets, new content, update all my info etc, but this is part of the jam. I have no interest in trying to find a record company, so I suppose it's up to me to make all this crap happen. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what's coming? Well, eventually this page will get a complete re-do. I'm going to continue to use this as a blog platform, as I have so many wonderful ideas to share. Mostly though new music is coming down the pipe line. I didn't waste my time off, I've got lots of tracks I'm working on right now and it's just a matter of deciding what I want to polish up for &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt;. I'd write more but I spent four hours getting everything back up and running and I'm frankly sick of staring at Vim editors. Yes, I use Vim and maintain this website my self. Why, jealous?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>news</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 13:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>