<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking (rant)</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/categories/rant.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 12:27:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola &lt;http://getnikola.com/&gt;</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Actin'fools</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/actinfools.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;As always, music first&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, my newest song: &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/nerd-plays-games"&gt;Nerd Plays Games&lt;/a&gt;. I think the title pretty well explains the song. I'm a nerd, I play games, I made a song about it. I doubt very much this will be the last time I feel like writing a song about games. I'm sure everyone will love it of course. If, in fact, you do love my music, I'd advise you to follow me on Twitter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/intent/user?screen_name=Al_Hacha"&gt;@Al_Hacha&lt;/a&gt; and on &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Another Day, Another Rant&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jesus H. Christ people, how stupid are you? Every time someone tries to monetize their site (which sits on a real server that costs real money to host) or to change the policies to expand their income, people on the Internet who rely on said service go ape shit. Now, that seems like I'm being a dick. These people use the service and then suddenly the policy changes, so why shouldn't they be mad? Isn't it right for someone who is used to being able to advertise for free using Facebook, to be upset when Facebook pushes down their posts in favor of ads? Shouldn't SoundCloud users be upset that they no longer have somewhere to publish their unlicensed remixes? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you didn't catch the tone there, I am being sarcastic. It's utter nonsense, every bit of it. Every time this happens and people on the Internet throw a fit, I can't help but think it's their fault. How? I'll explain. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/actinfools.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>music</category><category>rant</category><category>jerks</category><category>Facebook</category><category>Soundcloud</category><category>Hip-Hop</category><category>nerd</category><category>dork</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/actinfools.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 07:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Missing The Point</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;First, The Good News&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I uploaded my new track &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/clean-out-my-mind-1"&gt;Clean Out My Mind&lt;/a&gt;. It's a fun song, hopefully we'll see some action on the it. If anyone reads this and is interested in my other beats, I'm working as hard as I can on cleaning up my tracks and getting them ready. So be patient, very soon the world will be positively flooded with the sweet, soothing sounds of Al Hacha. As we speak I working on redesigning this site to reflect the change of focus and to maybe include some ways to buy my music, if you were so interested. Also, todays rant isn't so much pop culture as it is a personal gripe. Without further ado:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Onward!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm writing today about gear snobs. I frequent music blogs, forums and most often the popular rap production subreddit &lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/www.reddit.com/r/makinghiphop"&gt;Making Hip Hop&lt;/a&gt;. I've noticed a trend amongst the users of my various haunts: the proliferation of gear heads. That would be their own locution, I prefer to call them gear dicks. These guys love hanging out and letting people know that without the right gear, well, you're just screwed. You'll never make music as good as other people, these people of course, unless you step up and buy thousands of dollars of gear to make music. What a bunch of bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="more"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html"&gt;Read more…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>rant</category><category>jerks</category><category>music</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/missing-the-point.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 07:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>