<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>I Can't Stop Talking (Update)</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://www.icantstoptalking.com/categories/update.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 11:52:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola &lt;http://getnikola.com/&gt;</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Knock'n Boots</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/knockn-boots.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to all my fan(s?). Honestly, I'm almost certain no one is reading this, but it's fun to pretend!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of course, the new music: &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/lets-just-do-it"&gt;Lets Just Do It&lt;/a&gt; just "dropped" so to speak. It's far from studio quality, I know, but this is the first song I've been brave enough to publish with the vocals I recorded. It's not uncommon for me to rap over the beats I make, but I haven't ever done one that I felt could stand up to real scrutiny. By all means, this one could do with some scrutiny, but it could be a lot worse. It is about sexual congress, or "fucking" as the kids call it. It's not a curse laden &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u6VTj7LhCtE&amp;amp;feature=kp"&gt;2 Live Crew&lt;/a&gt; song, nor am I &lt;a href="http://youtu.be/Zyhu2ysqKGk"&gt;singing about juice running down my leg&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's odd, but sex is one of the easiest and hardest things to rhyme about. It's easy because, well, it's easy. Men think about it a lot, combine that with the ease of rhyming "ass", "fuck" and "titts" and you've got a pretty straightforward path. Any guy off the road could probably do a clumsy job of rapping about how much he likes Titts &amp;amp; Ass if you gave him a minute to think about it. The real challenge is talking about sex in a way that hasn't been done a million times already, but still comes off as clever. I mean, you could spend the entire song rapping about how big your dick is, which seems to be the most common go-to in rap. You could go the &lt;a href="http://www.cracked.com/blog/3-genius-artists-who-created-their-best-works-by-accident_p2/"&gt;Robert Plant&lt;/a&gt; route and try to make it "subtle". Either extreme and you're probably doing the exact same thing other people have already done. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried to split the difference. It's direct, there is some adult language, but I'm not falling over my self to make very explicit, gross lyrics. Everyone who's had sex knows the basics, I don't think you need me spelling out every step of the journey. Personally, I always got grossed when Easy-E put such detail and palaver into his sexual lyrics. On the other side, I'm not giving you heavy handed metaphor. This isn't the sixties, I'm pretty sure we're allowed to mention the fact that women can have orgasms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over all, I'm pretty happy with it. I hope anyone who gives it a listen enjoys it, and if so please don't forget to click the RSS button on top if you use Feedly, and give my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha/"&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt; a jingle-jangle. If you want to speak to me directly &lt;a href="mailto:icsttemp@gmail.com"&gt;give my email a go&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/154358434&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_artwork=true&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>music</category><category>Update</category><category>new release</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/knockn-boots.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 11:20:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moved On</title><link>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I moved, didn't have internet for four months, finally got it back up. Now I'm sorting through web stuff I haven't looked at in months. I am updating this page (work in progress, clearly) my &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt; profile and my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/al_hacha"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; account. It's dreary work, I'd rather work on music than make new art assets, new content, update all my info etc, but this is part of the jam. I have no interest in trying to find a record company, so I suppose it's up to me to make all this crap happen. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what's coming? Well, eventually this page will get a complete re-do. I'm going to continue to use this as a blog platform, as I have so many wonderful ideas to share. Mostly though new music is coming down the pipe line. I didn't waste my time off, I've got lots of tracks I'm working on right now and it's just a matter of deciding what I want to polish up for &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/al_hacha"&gt;Soundcloud&lt;/a&gt;. I'd write more but I spent four hours getting everything back up and running and I'm frankly sick of staring at Vim editors. Yes, I use Vim and maintain this website my self. Why, jealous?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Blog</category><category>Update</category><category>news</category><guid>http://www.icantstoptalking.com/posts/moved-on.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 13:36:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>